Winston Sharples Music Manuscripts
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Theatrical Cartoons, 1943-1967 (Box 1-14, 17-23)
  - Screen Songs, 1948-1951
    - Blue Hawaii (unknown number), 1950, Parts; Featured song: "Blue Hawaii" (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Boos in the night (SS-8-11), 1949, Parts; Featured song: "Pack up your troubles" (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Drippy Mississippi (unknown number), 1951, Parts; Featured song: "Mississippi" (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Fresh yeggs (SS-10-1), 1950, Parts; Featured song: "Give my regards to Broadway" (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Gobs of fun (SS-9-12), 1949, Full score and parts; Featured song: "Strike up the band" (Here comes a sailor) (parts only); Additional song: "Blow the man down" (full score only (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Heap hep injuns (SS-9-4), 1949, Parts and lyric sheet with cues; Featured song: "My pony boy" (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Helter swelter (unknown number), 1950, Parts; Featured song: "In the good old summertime" (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Jingle jangle jungle (unknown number), 1950, Parts; Featured song: "Civilization" (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Our funny finny friends (unknown number), 1949, Parts; Featured song: "Three little fishies" (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Readin', ritin' and rhythmetic (unknown number), 1948, Parts; Featured song: "School days" (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Short'nin' bread (SS-9-2), 1950, Parts and lyric sheets; Several versions; Featured song: "Short'nin' bread"; Additional song: "Cookie carnival" (lyrics only) (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Snow foolin' (unknown number), 1949, Part and lyric sheets; Featured song: "Jingle bells" (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Spring song (SS-8-5), 1949, Score, parts, and lyric sheets; Featured song: "Spring song", lyrics by Buddy Kaye (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Toys will be toys (unknown number), 1949, Parts; Featured song: "Oh! You beautiful doll" (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Tweet music (unknown number), 1951, Parts; Featured song: "Let's all sing like the birdies sing" (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Win, place and showboat (unknown number), 1950, Parts; Featured song: "Waitin' for the Robert E. Lee" (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Winter draws on (SS-7-2), 1948, Parts and cue sheets; Featured song: "Alabamy bound" (Box-folder 22/19)
  - Swifty and Shorty, 1964-1965
    - Accidents will happen (0549), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 5/8)
    - The bus way to travel (0552), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Call me a taxi (0542), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Fix that clock (0540), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Fizzicle fizzle (0537), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/3)
    - A Friend in tweed (0541), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Highway slobbery (0543), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Hip hop olè (0548), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Inferior decorator (0551), 1965, Particell (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Inferior decorator (0551), 1965, Full score (Box-folder 17/11)
    - The once over (0538), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Sailing zero (0535), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Service with a smile (0539), 1964, Particell (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Unidentified Titles (Famous Studios), circa 1956, 1960-1967
    - CG-18-5, circa late 1950s, Full score; Possibly a Casper the Friendly Ghost cartoon, based on job number prefix letters (Box-folder 19/1)
    - HK-17-5, circa 1959, Full score; Possibly a Herman and Katnip cartoon, based on job number prefix letters (Box-folder 19/2)
    - HK-18-6A, circa 1959, Full score; Possibly a Herman and Katnip cartoon, based on job number prefix letters (Box-folder 19/3)
    - N-17-9, circa 1958, Full score (Box-folder 19/4)
    - 0313, circa 1962, Full score (Box-folder 19/5)
    - 0321, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/6)
    - 0323, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/7)
    - 0328, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/8)
    - 0331, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/9)
    - 0332, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/10)
    - 0415, circa 1962, Full score (Box-folder 19/11)
    - 0513, circa 1962, Full score (Box-folder 19/12)
    - 0522, circa 1962, Full score (Box-folder 19/13)
    - 0523, circa 1962, Full score (Box-folder 19/14)
    - 0526, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/15)
    - 0528, circa 1963, Full score (Box-folder 19/16)
    - 0564, circa 1965, Full score (Box-folder 19/17)
    - 0568, circa 1965, Full score (Box-folder 19/18)
    - 0569, circa 1965, Full score (Box-folder 19/19)
    - 0570, circa 1965, Full score (Box-folder 19/20)
    - 0571, circa 1965, Full score (Box-folder 20/1)
    - 0577, circa 1966, Full score (Box-folder 20/2)
    - 0578, circa 1966, Full score (Box-folder 20/3)
    - 0579, circa 1966, Full score (Box-folder 20/4)
    - 0581, circa 1966, Full score; Score is labeled "Wilbur's song" (Box-folder 20/5)
    - 0582, circa 1966, Full score (Box-folder 20/6)
    - 0586, circa 1966, Full score (Box-folder 20/7)
    - 0587, circa 1966, Full score (Box-folder 20/8)
    - 0589, circa 1967, Full score (Box-folder 20/9)
    - 0590, circa 1967, Full score (Box-folder 20/10)
    - 0591, circa 1967, Full score (Box-folder 20/11)
    - 0626, 1967, Parts (Box-folder 23/1)
    - 0630, 1967, Particell (Box-folder 3/9)
    - 0630, 1967, Full score (Box-folder 20/12)
    - 0632, 1967, Particell (Box-folder 3/10)
    - 0632, 1967, Full score (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Music cues, nos. 28-47, circa 1960s, Full score (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Para. title (unknown number), circa 1962, Full score; Music used for the Comic Kings' Beetle Bailey series (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Telemeter # 1, circa 1956, Particell (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Title tags (unknown number), circa 1962, Full score; Introductory music for an unidentified Comic Kings series (Box-folder 21/4)
- Television Cartoons, circa 1963-1968 (Box 20-21, 23)
  Holograph manuscript full scores and instrumental parts for various 1960s television cartoon series that were produced by Joe Oriolo or Hal Seeger. Included are several stock music cues that were repeatedly used as part of the underscores.
  Arranged by production company, then alphabetically by series title and individual cartoon title therein.
  - Joe Oriolo Productions, circa 1963
    - The Mighty Hercules, 1963
      - The Mighty Hercules. Theme song, circa 1963, Full score; lyric sheet (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Hal Seeger Productions, circa 1965-1968
    - Flukey Luke, circa 1965
      - Flukey Luke. Unidentified title, circa 1965, Full scores (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Milton the Monster, 1965-1968
      - Milton the Monster. Music cues, circa 1965-1968, Full scores (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Milton the Monster. Music cues, circa 1965-1968, Full scores (Box-folder 23/11)
      - Milton the Monster. Music cues, nos. 1-57, circa 1965-1968, Full scores (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Milton the Monster. Music cues, nos. 1-27, circa 1965-1968, Full scores (Box-folder 23/13-14)
      - Milton the Monster. Music cues, circa 1965-1968, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Penny the Penguin, circa 1965
      - Penny the penguin. Unidentified title, circa 1965, Full score (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Super Blooper, circa 1965
      - Super Blooper. Miscellaneous non-titled scores, sketches, circa 1965, Full scores (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Unidentified Titles: Unknown Cartoon Series, circa 1960s
    - Music cues, circa 1960s
      - Music cues (nos. 1-35), circa 1960s, Full scores (Box-folder 23/16-17)
- Live Action Films, 1940s-1950s (Box 15-16, 21, 24-30)
  Music composed for live action short films and documentaries produced by Paramount and other companies. In addition, full scores and/or parts for twelve episodes of His Honor, Homer Bell.
  Arranged alphabetically by production company, and by individual title therein. Unidentified film titles are listed separately, including working titles (if present), and other details. The His Honor, Homer Bell scores are listed separately and arranged numerically by original episode number.
  - Shorts and Documentaries, 1940s-1950s
    - Bransby Productions, undated
      - Land called New Jersey, undated, Full score; Three reels; Also included: several annotated cue sheets (Box-folder 24/1-2)
    - Paramount Pictures, Inc., circa late 1940s
      - Bundle from Brazil, 1948, Full score; Film is from Paramount's Pacemaker series (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Bundle from Brazil, 1948, Score with cues; Film is from Paramount's Pacemaker series (Box-folder 26/1)
      - The grass is greener, undated, Full score; Three reels (Box-folder 16/2-4)
      - The grass is greener, undated, Instrumental parts; Three reels (Box-folder 24/3-7)
      - Paramount News, circa late 1940s, Scores (musical cues) (Box-folder 25/1-8)
    - United States Information Service, undated
      - Men of the forest, undated, Full score; Six reels (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Unknown production company, circa early 1950s
      - Westinghouse, circa 1952, Full score; Three reels (Box-folder 16/5-7)
      - Unidentified documentary, undated, Full score (Box-folder 16/11)
      - Unidentified documentary, undated, Full score; Brief individual musical selections; Includes miscellaneous cue notes (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Television Programs, 1955
    - Galahad Productions/NBC Films, 1955
      - His Honor, Homer Bell, 1955
        - Introductory theme music, 1955, Piano score (Box-folder 27/1)
        - Episode #1 - The young at heart, 1955, Instrumental part (fragment) (Box-folder 27/3)
        - Episode #7 - The piano lesson, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/1)
        - Episode #7 - The piano lesson, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 27/4-5)
        - Episode #8 - Cousin Edwin's visit, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/2)
        - Episode #8 - Cousin Edwin's visit, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 27/6-8)
        - Episode #9 - The courtship, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/3)
        - Episode #9 - The courtship, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 28/1-3)
        - Episode #11 - The cook nappers, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/4)
        - Episode #11 - The cook nappers, 1955, Instrumental parts; Includes cue notes (Box-folder 28/4-6)
        - Episode # 14 - Aunt Catherine, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/5)
        - Episode #14 - Aunt Catherine, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 28/7-8)
        - Episode #16 - The farm, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/6)
        - Episode #16 - The farm, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 29/1-2)
        - Episode #17 - The dog story, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/7)
        - Episode #17 - The dog story, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 29/3-5)
        - Episode #21 - The black eye, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/8)
        - Episode #21 - The black eye, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 29/6-8)
        - Episode #23 - Red tape, 1955, Full score (fragment) (Box-folder 15/9)
        - Episode #23 - Red tape, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 30/1)
        - Episode #24 - The gift, 1955, Instrumental parts; Title is believed to be a working title. It does not appear on the complete 38 episode list (Box-folder 30/2)
        - Episode #27 - The art contest, 1955, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 30/3-4)
        - Episode unknown - Dreamboat, 1955, Cue and timing notes only (Box-folder 27/2)
        - Episode # unknown - unidentified title, 1955, Full score (Box-folder 15/10)
        - Episode # unknown - unidentified title, 1955, Full score; Page 1 is missing (Box-folder 15/11)
- Miscellany, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 16, 21, 23, 30)
  Music, sketches, lyrics, and other materials that have not been identified as having been used as film music. Includes music containing partial titles, music credited to other composers, and music with no title information. Full or partial titles are provided if present.
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Song Sheets, circa 1940s
    - Be's ya got bugs, circa 1940s, Lyric sheet; Uncredited (Box-folder 23/18)
    - I take an oath, circa 1940s, Lyric sheet; Lyrics by Al J. Neiburg; music by Sammy Timberg, Winston Sharples (Box-folder 23/19)
    - In a cozy corner, circa 1948, Score and lyric sheet; Arrangement of an old standard song (Box-folder 23/20)
    - In my calendar of dreams, circa 1940s, Lyric sheet and piano part; Lyrics by Al J. Neiburg; music by Sammy Timberg, Winston Sharples (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Nobody knows where the man in the moon goes, circa 1940s, Lyric sheet; Lyrics by Al J. Neiburg; music by Sammy Timberg, Winston Sharples (Box-folder 23/22)
    - Oh dem golden slippers, circa 1946, Score (Box-folder 23/23)
    - The reunion waltz, circa 1940s, Lyric sheet; Uncredited (Box-folder 23/24)
    - Superwhite, circa late 1940s, Score; Uncredited; Possibly a toothpaste jingle (Box-folder 23/25)
    - Wedding of two broken hearts, circa 1940s, Score and lyric sheet; Uncredited (Box-folder 23/26)
    - Who are you?, circa 1940s, Score and lyric sheet; Uncredited (Box-folder 23/27)
    - You can do, circa 1940s, Lyric sheet; Uncredited (Box-folder 23/28)
  - Unidentified Music, Sketches and Fragments, undated
    - Unidentified film music. The colossal show, undated, Full score (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Unidentified film music. The colossal show, undated, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Unidentified film music. Manhattan, undated, Full score (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Unidentified film music. Maryland, undated, Full score (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Unidentified film music. Pied piper, undated, Full score (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Unidentified film music. Square dances, undated, Instrumental parts (Box-folder 30/7-8)
    - Unidentified film music. Sullivan's column, undated, Full score; Fragment (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Unidentified music. C.P. species I-V, undated, Piano scores (2) (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Unidentified music. Choruses I-II, undated, Full score (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Unidentified music. Dram. opening; Dram. F.F., undated, Piano score (Box-folder 30/10)
    - Unidentified music. Main title, undated, Full score (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Unidentified music. Main title, undated, Full score (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Unidentified music. R.H.H. cues, undated, Piano score (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Unidentified music. With music by Tchaikowsky, undated, Melodic line only (Box-folder 30/12)
    - Unidentified music sketches, undated, Piano score (Box-folder 30/13)
    - Unidentified music tablets, undated, Piano music; Music staff tablets (2) (Box-folder 30/14)
  - Music by Other Composers, undated
    - Poulenc, Francis
      - L'embarquement pour Cythère: for two pianos, undated, Manuscript piano parts (Box-folder 30/15)
    - Trolli, Nilo
      - Harlequin: scherzo for piano, undated, Manuscript score (Box-folder 30/16)